

MARIA FLORENCIA CHIALVO

Software Engineer

Barcelona, Spain

mf.chialvo@gmail.com (+549) 1160209663

Solid professional career in software development on multiple technologies, with experience in the development of services and products in multidisciplinary teams

Over the past few years, I have taken on leadership roles, managing and guiding teams to success.

My focus is on promoting a collaborative environment, driving creative solutions and ensuring the delivery of high-quality projects.

SKILLS

- Extensive technical knowledge.
- Mentoring and leadership experience.
- Experience in project management and planning.
- Work with agile methodologies.

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Spanish Native

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Manager PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Jan 2024 - Present

Leadership of the shopping cart and price calculation team. My main responsibilities include planning, coordination and dependency management of our projects. I foster a positive and agile work culture, and I am in charge of developing talent within the team.

Principal Software Engineer PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Mar 2022 - Dec 2023

Technical leadership in the fintech tribe working with microservices (Kotlin, Go + AWS). Responsible for the design and implementation of maintainable and scalable solutions, coordinating with other teams, and promoting good development practices seeking the best balance to maximize the value delivered.

Software Engineer Backend PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Jul 2020 - Feb 2022

Analysis and development in the wallet team, implementing solutions in different languages such as Kotlin and Go in a microservices ecosystem.

Software Engineer Full Stack Almundo | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Nov 2017- Jun 2020

Mar 2014- Oct 2017

Analysis and development, implementing solutions with various backend and frontend technologies such as Java, Rust, NodeJs, Angular and AngularJS for web applications.

Software Engineer Full Stack BDF Technology Solutions | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Analysis and development, implementing solutions with various backend and frontend technologies such as Java, JavaScript, AngularJS, NodeJS and PrimeFaces for web and desktop applications.

EDUCATION

Information Systems Engineering, completed UTN FRBA | Buenos Aires, Argentina

2011 - 2016